<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thomas Laber</title>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thomas Laber</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 4</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/linear-regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/linear-regression/</guid>
      <description>Source https://www.analyticsvidhya.com/blog/2017/09/common-machine-learning-algorithms/
It is used to estimate real values (cost of houses, number of calls, total sales etc.) based on continuous variable(s). Here, we establish relationship between independent and dependent variables by fitting a best line. This best fit line is known as regression line and represented by a linear equation $$Y= a *X + b$$ The best way to understand linear regression is to relive this experience of childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Good They Can&#39;t Ignore You</title>
      <link>http://example.com/book/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/book/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/</guid>
      <description>Source https://commoncog.com/blog/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/
19-25 Minuten
Cal Newport&amp;rsquo;s 2012 book So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You is a career strategy book designed around four ideas.
 The first idea is that &amp;lsquo;follow your passion&amp;rsquo; is terrible career advice, and people who say this should be shot don&amp;rsquo;t know what they&amp;rsquo;re talking about. Cal Newport calls this idea of following your passion &amp;lsquo;the passion hypothesis&amp;rsquo;.
 The second idea is that instead of believing in the passion hypothesis, you should adopt what Newport calls the &amp;lsquo;craftsman mindset&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Hypothesis</title>
      <link>http://example.com/book/the-happiness-hypothesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/book/the-happiness-hypothesis/</guid>
      <description>##The Divided Self
Human thinking depends on metaphor. We understand new or complex things in relation to things we already know. For example, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to think about life in general, but once you apply the metaphor &amp;ldquo;life is a journey,&amp;rdquo; the metaphor guides you to some conclusions: You should learn the terrain, pick a direction, find some good traveling companions, and enjoy the trip, because there may be nothing at the end of the road.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>